iphone-network.net 2011-12-30

# Privacy | iPhone-Network.net

## Privacy

**Privacy Policy**

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at webmaster@iphone-network.net.

At iPhone-Network.net, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by iPhone-Network.net and how it is used.

Log Files  
Like many other Web sites, iPhone-Network.net makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

Cookies and Web Beacons  
iPhone-Network.net does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

DoubleClick DART Cookie

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on iPhone-Network.net .  
.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to iPhone-Network.net and other sites on the Internet  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include …….  
Google Adsense

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on iPhone-Network.net send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

iPhone-Network.net has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. iPhone-Network.net privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

**DMCA Information**

iPhone-Network.net is in compliance with 17 U.S.C. § 512 and the Digital Millennium Copyright Act (“DMCA”). It is our policy to respond to any infringement notices and take appropriate actions under the Digital Millennium Copyright Act (“DMCA”) and other applicable intellectual property laws.

If your copyrighted material has been posted on iPhone-Network.net or if links to your copyrighted material are returned through our search engine and you want this material removed, you must provide a written communication that details the information listed in the following section. Please be aware that you will be liable for damages (including costs and attorneys’ fees) if you misrepresent information listed on our site that is infringing on your copyrights. We suggest that you first contact an attorney for legal assistance on this matter.

The following elements must be included in your copyright infringement claim :

Provide evidence of the authorized person to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed.

Provide sufficient contact information so that we may contact you. You must also include a valid email address.

You must identify in sufficient detail the copyrighted work claimed to have been infringed and including at least one search term under which the material appears in iPhone-Network.net’s search results.

A statement that the complaining party has a good faith belief that use of the material in the manner complained of is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law.

A statement that the information in the notification is accurate, and under penalty of perjury, that the complaining party is authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed.

Must be signed by the authorized person to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly being infringed.

Send the written infringement notice to the following address and an email notifcation to **webmaster@iPhone-Network.net**  
Please allow 1-2 business days for an email response. Note that emailing your complaint to other parties such as our Internet Service Provider will not expedite your request and may result in a delayed response due the complaint not properly being filed.

#### Sign up Free Email Newsletter

Stay Updates with this Blog. Get Free email newsletter updates, **Enter your Email here:**

Don't forget to confirm your email subcription

### Leave your comment here:

You must be [logged in](http://www.iphone-network.net/wp-login.php?redirect_to=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.iphone-network.net%2Fprivacy%2F) to post a comment.
